# Gijs Wels





05/29/1997



+31611856348



gijswels@gmail.com



Amsterdam



gijswels.github.io

## Qualities

- ◆ Independant
- ◆ Team player
- ◆ Curious
- ◆ Creative thinking
- Solution oriented

# Languages











# **Industrial Design Engineer**

I am an industrial designer with a focus on physical products and the relationships we create between people and their world through design - the new behaviours and experiences they enable. I have a special interest in well-being, innovation, and good design, both aesthetically and practically. I learned that it is not only important to dream but also to realise. This results in a hardworking person who motivates those around him to achieve the same goals - to make things happen!

### Education

# MSc Integrated Product Design

May 29, 2024

TU Delft, Delft

» Product(-service) design, concept design, and technical prototyping.

## BSc Industrial Design Engineering

2021

U Delft, Delf

» Technology, bussiness, people, and design.

#### Minor Architecture

2019

TU Delft, Delf

» House of the future, analysing global trends, and spatial design and planning.

VWO+
s.g. Spieringshoek, Schiedam

2015

## Extracurricular

#### Ambassadeurs van Amsterdam

09/2024 - 12/2024

Amsterdan

» Tackling a societal issue, developing a project plan in a diverse group and running a pilot.

#### Summer School

07/2023 - 08/2023

Aalto University, Helsinki

» Design environments in balance with nature in an international and multidisciplinary group.

### Exchange

01/2023 - 06/2023

Chalmers University, Gothenburg

» UX, form & manufacturing, manufacturing strategy, and introduction in data science & Al.

### Internship

09/2020 - 02/2021

DigiNova, Delf

» UX, UI, and development. A music application for robots for elderly with dementia.

# **Employment**

#### Royal Ahrend

10/2023 - 05/2024

Office Furniture, Sint-Oedenrode

» Graduation project. Studying behaviour, work culture and employee well-being (stress).

#### MBO Rijnland

02/2019 - 06/2019

Secretary School, Godd

Teaching assistent.

# Frankeland

08/2012 - 02/2023

Nursing Home, Schiedam

» Host. Bridge between elderly and management.

# **Noteworthy Achievements**

#### Micro-Break Communication Tool

Royal Ahrend, Sint-Oedenrode

By creating social awareness the goal is to counter the rising trend of burnout complaints.

Natural Seating

2023

2024

Aalto University, Helsinki

Seat to connect with nature; focus on functionality, minimalistic design and biodegradability.

I got selected by my faculty to participate in an international and multidisciplinary project about the use of wood in balance with nature.

High difficulty. An ergonomically almost impossible task, but I fondly look back on it. Ahrend

wants to release the chair in the future.

I graduated with a 9 out of 10 for my Master

thesis. I got selected to speak at the Vital Work

event hosted by the Workplace Vitality Hub.

Adjustable School Chair

Royal Ahrend, Sint-Oedenrode

Desk chair for Dutch primary education; adjustable to all students from the age of 5 to 12.

Adaptable City Square

2021

The Green Village, Delft

Of all thirty participating students, my solution got selected by the organisation to continue.

Bachelor thesis; green solution to the urban heat island effect in the municipality of Delft.















# urban oasis





# nature's seat



### Skills

## 3D Modelling

Rhinoceros Drawing

### Visual Communication

Adobe Illustrator Adobe Photoshop Adobe InDesign Adobe Premiere

### Digital Prototyping

Adobe Dreamweaver Figma Adobe XD Arduino Raspberry

### Physical Prototyping

Rapid Prototyping Workshop Experienced

#### I know my way around

JavaScript Python Mathlab Arduino Raspberry Pi